欢迎使用 MeoFind
Welcome to MeoFind
macOS 平台的全能文件管理器与预览工具
A universal file manager and preview tool for macOS
chapter-2
核心功能概览
📁 双面板文件浏览，支持列表与缩略图两种视图
📁 Dual-pane file browsing with list and thumbnail views
🔍 内置预览面板，支持 50+ 种文件格式
🔍 Built-in preview panel supporting 50+ file formats
chapter-3
预览功能详解
图片预览支持缩放、旋转、取色器
Image preview with zoom, rotate, and color picker
Office 文档可在 纯文本 和 格式化 间切换
Office docs switchable between text and formatted views
支持 PDF 搜索、代码语法高亮、Markdown 渲染
PDF search, code highlighting, Markdown rendering
chapter-4
高级特性
压缩包内文件列表预览（zip, tar, rar, 7z）
Archive content listing preview (zip, tar, rar, 7z)
预览窗口可弹出为独立窗口
Detachable preview window for multi-monitor setups
文件名快速搜索与正则表达式过滤
Quick file search with regex filtering
chapter-5
了解更多
访问官网 meofind.app 了解更多功能
Visit meofind.app for more information
感谢观看！
Thank you for watching!